Kori Umemura

fullstack developer

Osaka

imameugenau2k@gmail.com

+81 3 2911 7917

After graduating from university, I entered the IT world.

From writing web programming to writing mobile programming, I have devoted a lot of time to learning various skills.

From 4 years ago, I entered the blockchain world.

I am focus on developing smart contracts on Ethereum, Polygon, BSC and Solana Chain with solidity and rust language.

Blockchain has become a part of my life now.

I am looking for opportunities to work talented team or company.

I hope to learn more and to become a famous person like Satoshi.

Work Experience

BlockChain Developer

Retail Ecommerce Ventures - Remote October 2019 to April 2022

Full-stack web developer

Magnetic Asia Limited - Sheung Wan, Hong Kong Island February 2017 to August 2019

Front End Developer

Hachiraku Co. , Ltd - Sendagaya, Shibuya-ku October 2014 to December 2016

Education

Associate's degree in Computer Science

Osaka University - Osaka, Japan 2011 to 2014

Skills

- MySQL (5 years)
- AWS (3 years)
- Angular (3 years)
- MongoDB (6 years)
- Java (5 years)
- Front-End Development (8 years)

- Web Services (4 years)
- Software Development (8 years)
- GitHub (8 years)
- Go (4 years)
- Unit Testing
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- XML
- APIs (5 years)
- User Interface (UI)
- SQL (6 years)
- Solidity (4 years)
- Rust (3 years)
- Go (3 years)
- Solana (2 years)
- Ethereum (3 years)
- Cardano (3 years)
- Avalanche (2 years)
- Polygon (1 year)
- Fantom (3 years)

Languages

- English Fluent
- Japanese Expert

Links

https://dev.to/smile0307

https://github.com/smile930307

https://medium.com/@smile0307

https://smile0307personalsite.netlify.app